[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
SHELDON:
Leonard? Leonard? Leonard?
(Penny:)What is it?
I made tea.
(Leonard:)I don't want tea.
(Sheldon:)I didn't make tea for you.
(Sheldon:)This is my tea.
(Leonard:)Then why are you telling me?
(Sheldon:)It's a conversation starter.
(Leonard:)That's a lousy conversation starter.
(Sheldon:)Oh, is it? We're conversing.
Checkmate.
(Leonard:)What do you want, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)What I want is to be departing
the starship Enterprise...
...in a one-man shuttlecraft
headed to the planetoid I rule...
(Sheldon:)...known as Sheldon Alpha Five.
Mm, I want that too.
(Leonard:)Why are you here?
(Sheldon:)To comfort you, of course.
(Sheldon:)No, that's not going to work at all.
I'll comfort you from over here.